They tried to electrocute "Meat Cleaver" Max. It didn't work.
The Horror Show is a horror, thriller, fantasy film directed by James Isaac.
Vowing revenge on the detective who apprehended him, serial killer "Meat Cleaver" Max
Jenke returns from beyond the grave to launch a whole new reign of terror.
Detective Lucas McCarthy, played by Lance Henriksen.
Max Jenke, played by Brion James.
Donna McCarthy, played by Rita Taggart.
Bonnie McCarthy, played by Dedee Pfeiffer.
Scott McCarthy, played by Aron Eisenberg.
Peter Campbell, played by Thom Bray.
The Rocky Horror Picture Show is a 1975 independent musical comedy horror film produced by Lou
Adler and Michael White, directed by Jim Sharman, and distributed by 20th Century Fox.
The screenplay was written by Sharman and Richard O'Brien,
who also played the supporting role Riff Raff.
The film is based on the 1973 musical stage production The Rocky
Horror Show, with music, book, and lyrics by O'Brien.
The production is a tribute to the science fiction and horror B
movies of the 1930s through to the early 1960s.
The film stars Tim Curry (in his debut), Susan Sarandon, and Barry Bostwick.
It is narrated by Charles Gray, with cast members from the original Royal Court Theatre, Roxy
Theatre, and Belasco Theatre productions, including Nell Campbell and Patricia Quinn.
The story centres on a young engaged couple whose car breaks down in
the rain near a castle, where they search for help.
The castle is occupied by strangers in elaborate costumes holding a party.
They then meet the head of the house, Dr.
Frank-N-Furter, an apparently mad scientist and alien transvestite from the planet Transsexual
in the galaxy of Transylvania, who creates a living muscle man named Rocky.
The film was shot in the United Kingdom at Bray Studios and on location at Oakley Court, a
country house best known for its earlier use by Hammer Film Productions.
A number of props and set pieces were reused from the Hammer horror films.
Although the film is both a parody of and tribute to many kitsch science fiction and horror
films, costume designer Sue Blane conducted no research for her designs.
Blane has claimed that her creations for the film directly affected the development of punk
rock fashion trends, such as torn fishnet stockings and colourfully dyed hair.
Initially the film was largely ignored by critics, but it soon became a hit as a midnight movie, when
audiences began participating with the film at the Waverly Theater in New York City in 1976.
Audience members returned to the cinemas frequently and talked back to the screen and began
dressing as the characters, spawning similar performance groups across the United States.
At almost the same time, fans in costume began performing alongside the film.
This "shadow cast" mimed the actions on screen, above and behind
them, while lip-synching their characters' lines.
Still in limited release in 2026, 50 years after its premiere, it is
the longest-running theatrical release in film history.
In many cities, live amateur shadow-casts act out the film as it is being shown
and heavily draw upon a tradition of audience participation.
The film is most often shown close to Halloween.
Today, the film has a large international cult following and has been
considered by many as one of the greatest musical films of all time.
In 2005, it was selected for preservation in the United States National Film Registry by the
Library of Congress as being "culturally, historically, or aesthetically significant."
The tone is dark and intense.